Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride the waves!
We're all together as one,
so let's stay away the sun!
All our dreams are never-ending,
Heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have
traveled different paths.
We are best friends.
Our freedom is our only compass.
That's pointing us along the
many roads that come together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon.
We'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
If the winds blow, it's really
where we should be going, go.
And friend, we're
shining, running forever.
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever.
The sea is coming out, so ride away.
We're all together as one,
so let's escape with a stun.
While our dreams are never ending.
Heartbeat, we will be one of your hands.
My darkness will swallow the world.
Just you wait and see.
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates
Roger's treasure belongs to me
We'll ride non-stop and travel farther
than we've ever gone And then tomorrow
we will find suspense And then commence
to live out another day so intense
That's right, we're shining,
running forever Let's go along
with curiosity Our feelings lead
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
running forever Open the map inside your
heart and see No matter where we end up,
our minds will never give up There's a fire
in our dreams and you can never, never,
never, never stop it We
will be one, go ahead!
With this fake grape
made out of Tata Babasco.
I'm gonna knock her out!
What was it?
See just if they be.
He sniped a fly?
No room for failure.
Operation SOP is a go!
He might be able to shoot
a fly mid-air, but not me!
I'm faster!
Dang, Leo's pretty quick!
Maybe he can pull this off!
We'll rescue our captured
compatriots no matter what!
Goal! Come on, Leo!
You can do it!
Please, let this plan work!
Wait, wait!
Huh?
Isn't it kind of weird that we haven't
had any new workers in nearly a year?
Yeah, I heard they don't even
visit the palace anymore.
Who's slacking on the clock?
Not us!
You would think when 500 of
you people don't return home,
you'd start to worry something's up.
And yet the Tontadas
don't suspect a thing.
They are so incredibly dumb.
I mean, pure-hearted.
So why do you think
they stopped showing up?
No clue.
Well, if we can't enslave anymore,
we'll have to work the butts
off the 500 we already have.
How about some job now?
What gives?
This smile fruit doesn't
look ripe enough yet!
Are you okay?
Start talking.
I thought Tontata could grow
anything, so what's with this crap?
We usually can.
These smile fruits aren't
exactly natural, though.
Hey, no excuses!
Could you give my brother a
few minutes to rest, please?
Today's meal was a little
bit spoiled, you see.
Now you're complaining about the food?
Want to cure your princess?
You know just how sick Mon Cherie is.
Yes, yes we do.
Then get your ass back
to farming more fruit.
You know they're an essential
ingredient in making her medication,
or did you forget?
The number of acceptable
fruits you produce in one
season is less than 10 %
of what you're harvesting.
You need to find a way to
increase your productivity.
Do you think we could
see Princess Moncheree?
No way.
Why not, though?
Because if you were to contract her
illness, we would be devastated. Huh?
We would never forgive
ourselves if we allowed anything
terrible to happen to our
beloved Tuntada partners.
Aw, Mr. Underling.
We're going to push ourselves
to work even harder.
Please continue to take
good care of our princess.
All right.
They're so gullible, I almost feel bad.
Why, Robaland?
Why stop me? I'm sorry.
However, if I hadn't done something,
then you would have gotten hurt.
Huh?
That fly he sniped?
He somehow shot it right between the eyes.
Treble's vision must be exceptional.
And his aim.
I believe it's far too
dangerous to approach Sugar.
While he's watching over her.
So, you got anything for a plan B?
That goes there
Hey, what's up with this cargo?
It's a swarm of pink ornets!
I have an urgent report from Mr.
Trouble.
Sir, we have a problem.
Captain Eve's pirates are causing
a disturbance in Sector 4.
They are demanding to speak to an
executive about renegotiating the price.
Hmm, they think they don't have
to be afraid of Joker anymore.
That takes some nerve!
Hey, you're not the regular messenger,
are you?
He's on a lunch break right now.
That's all—it's an emergency.
There's already been a few.
few New casualties reported!
Please, come quickly!
Casualties, huh?
Okay...
Hey! Hey!
Yes, Trouble?
Are you headed somewhere?
Tighten up security at the four doors
to the Executive Tower. Yes, sir!
And if anything goes wrong, do
let me know at once. Yes, sir!
Master Treble, keep up the good work, sir.
Hey, hey.
So where is he? Where's
the fight? This way.
I could handle this mess easily.
Yeah, right.
I'm staying safe.
But I think I should let you guys do it.
To build up your self-confidence.
Confidence.
And don't worry.
If anything goes wrong, I'll
jump in and take over, okay?
Well, that's good to know.
Huh?
Someone there?
We're here on a mission.
Whatever it takes,
we are going to rescue our friends
who are enslaved here in the factory.
But first, we're going to knock
you out cold, sugar! But why?
You're so mean, I don't know
anything about your friends.
Really? Truly?
Yeah. Aw, it's okay.
You're being fooled!
It's not okay!
Oh, close one!
You'll free our friends now!
Who brought you up to this?
We've been cheating you for ages,
and you little dimwits
never had so much as a clue.
I was curious.
You used to come to the
palace all the time,
but I haven't seen you in the past year.
I guess somebody has
been leading you astray.
Attack!
Hang her mouth open and hold her still!
I'm not amused.
I don't like it when
people think I'm weak.
Now you're all little black bears!
The contract.
Oh no, she turned us into toys!
You shall follow my every
order until the day you perish.
Don't tell me they
forgot about us already!
A bear army?
Where did all those
teddy soldiers come from?
And weren't we in the middle
of something just now?
Kill everyone in the executive
tower and do it immediately!
I can't disobey her orders!
Kill everyone?
Including me?
Please, I don't want to do this!
Those bears must be working for Sugar.
I thought the only one she
had guarding her was Treble,
but it looks like we were wrong.
Leo, it's me, Flapper!
All right, guys, get the enemy!
No! No! No! No!
Treble, come back at once!
Give us a trap!
Treble!
Huh?
A trap?
Hey!
Master Treble, please look!
They're all starting to fight!
It's utter chaos!
You have to do something!
Huh?
Hey, hey! You guys okay?
I heard there's a dilemma.
Master trouble!
Well, go on now.
Well, it's basically nothing, sir.
We're just a bit jumpy because
we found hornets in our cargo.
Rest assured, this won't
have any effect on our deal.
She did lie.
Hey, hey, wait!
Here comes trouble!
Nice try! Hey, hey!
Who exactly are you, uh, a spy?
Where did she go? Hey! Hey!
Wait a second, I know her!
She's in the strike!
That crew, how'd she get down here?
Dragon Ball!
Why are they going after Sugar?
Get back up here.
You were fooled, you
good-for-nothing idiot.
Die! Ah!
I'm mad now!
Stinky, stinky, shay!
Stick, stick him!
Meteora!
I...
I think Master Trouble is going crazy!
The executive tower, it's gonna wreck it!
Usopp!
Usopp, wake up!
I was worried. Robin! Shh!
What happened?
Did we just get crushed by a big duck?
The tentata have all been captured.
Drop dead, you crap head!
Why don't you die first, you little brat?
Anyway, we're having a
serious conversation.
So buzz off, you ready to talk yet?
I just said I'm not talking.
Good boy.
Keep Usuland safe.
Let's run while we still can, Robin.
Truth is, he's a friend of mine.
You can tell me. He is?
Oh, yeah.
His name is...
You mean Usuland? No!
You sure are dumb.
Um, you really think
he's my friend? Oh, no!
I fell right into your trap!
Are you friends with that
one-legged soldier, too? I...
I'm not telling.
Well, I already know.
Oh, guess I can talk about it, then.
Yeah, he's our friend.
Actually, I didn't know. I'm a fool!
Interesting.
I'm finally getting a clear picture now.
Uh, it doesn't matter if you know or not.
You guys are finished either way!
We're bringing them back no matter what!
Since we're sharing secrets
right now, I'll tell you it too.
Is everyone okay?
Yo, buddy.
Gotta be more careful.
You should have made him angry.
You guys gave it your best shot.
But Treble is out of our league.
I can still fight.
We won't give up.
We'll finish Operation SOB.
Our friends are counting on us.
I believe in the commander.
We have to help him defeat Doflamingo.
We won't stop until he does.
He's waiting for us.
And we cannot let him down!
There's no time to waste!
Commander, no!
He's leaving the warlords?
I don't get it.
So he's stepping down
from the throne, too?
What's going to happen to us?
He's nothing now.
A plain old pirate.
The Navy won't let him
get away with his crimes.
And this coliseum's going
to be the first thing to go.
Commander, did you see the newspaper?
Well, get our friends back.
And we don't even have to fight!
Just think of how many
lives will be saved by this!
We're lucky! No.
It was a false report.
It was a lie?
He's not leaving after all! All right!
Doflamenco's a great king!
There's no reason why he
should ever step down!
Our kingdom is saved!
I'm going to enter today's competition
and win the Plain Plain Fruit!
And then, I'll be able
to defeat Doflamingo!
That's foolish!
Have patience.
I know that you're angry,
and I feel the same way.
But the end is at hand.
My forces are ready to fight.
I can handle this myself.
I've waited! Long enough!
Our hopes have been dropped
from heaven to hell.
The fighters can't take this anymore!
Their spirits are broken!
All we can do now is
wait till the day we die.
They say they'll release us if
we survive a thousand times.
But how is that supposed to give us hope?
It's just more misery.
The gladiator Kiros won
all 3 ,000 of his matches.
But that's just a stupid legend.
No one even remembers him.
Kiros was probably made
up by a bunch of prisoners
who were holding on to
a dream of being free.
But he's just a statue.
A perfect warrior who
could never really exist.
I'm sick of dreaming an
impossible dream, so I'll fight.
The competition today is my
one chance, so I'm taking it!
It's a suicide mission!
We're not talking about a
typical gladiator match.
You'll end up dead.
I forbid you to enter.
You are not thinking straight.
You are only 16.
Rebecca, I simply know better than you.
Trust me.
You're not an adult yet.
You don't know what's good for you.
Oh, shut up!
Stop acting like you're my father!
You are the one who's not
thinking straight here.
You can handle this!
I don't know what your plan is,
but you can't beat the flamingo.
Look at yourself!
You're just a broken toy with one leg!
Of course.
You're right.
Wait!
I'm sorry for being so menacing,
but if you can, please do not fight.
Seltzer!
We can talk!
Just come back!
Seltzer, please!
Don't leave like this!
I'm scared!
I didn't want you to
sacrifice yourself, okay?
That's all!
I'm sorry!
I'm just so worried about you!
Please, come back!
This is the first time I've
ever seen Rebecca attack!
She's going on the offensive!
Hold on, what's with that sword?
The blade isn't even sharp, is it?
In this coliseum we fight
to the death if you won't
shed the blood of others
You'll pay with your own.
That's what the audience
wants to see after all now
Damn!
Hey! Muscle melon!
Are you talking to me?
Protect her for me, okay?
Whaaaaat?
Say, Rebecca, here's a question.
Do you happen to know how
your dear Mother Scarlet died?
I'm going to bring us something to eat.
I saw the toy soldier that day.
He cried like a baby. Pathetic.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I failed to protect your mother.
That's not just my legs.
Pika must be moving.
I wonder if he's dealing
with someone as well.
Stay right there.
Are you all right, Commander?
Yes, thank you.
We've got to move! Hold on.
They'll be hurt if we don't help them.
Get your paws off me,
young little bastards!
Stop looking back, Commander. Just go!
We're ready.
We all knew what we signed up for.
Don't say that.
If you stay here, then everyone might die.
Even if Leo pulls off Operation
SOP, it's still not over.
If we let Doflamingo walk away, he
can do the same thing all over again.
Or even worse!
No one else can beat Toe Flamingo.
We're counting on you for that.
Keep fighting!
Is the commander really
such a big deal, Leo?
I don't know.
Seems kind of crazy to
bet everything on one guy.
Why do you trust him so much?
He's just a one-legged toy!
Normally, when Sugar
turns someone into a toy,
they're bound by the contract she makes.
meaning they can't disobey.
That's why they're able to
keep them all as slaves.
But unlike them, the commander's free.
He was the first one
here to be transformed.
So that time when Sugar
used her hobby-hobby power,
she made a mistake and forgot
to form a contract with him.
One little error from
more than ten years ago
gave them a powerful
enemy like none other.
He's the only toy in this kingdom who can
strike back at the Don Quixote family.
A toy who can take revenge for them all.
For a whole decade,
he's been fighting on his own, but he
never gave up and he never lost hope.
He knew the truth about the toys
and how much they were suffering,
slaving away and forgotten.
In time, all our people would
have been enslaved as well,
but thanks to him, now
we're able to fight back.
If he calls us to arms, we have to answer!
Otherwise, this kingdom
is as good as dead!
He's worth it!
We're proud to bet
everything we've got on him!
Nobody remembers him now, but years ago,
everyone in the kingdom knew who he was.
Before he got transformed into
a toy, his name was Kiros.
He was the strongest gladiator
that the Colosseum had ever seen.
That's who our commander is.
A legendary hero.